anyway I've been married 35 years this
year
yeah yeah it's it's a long time it's uh
it's a really really long time actually
I I remember when we got married Pastor
said till death do you part and I was
like all right I didn't think I'd live
this long to be honest with you it's uh
it's a little longer than I anticipated
but I'm lucky cuz my wife is great and I
I definitely married out of my league
she is way better person than I am in
almost every way she uh she is I but I
think all men marry out of their league
honestly I think if you're a man and
you're married you're out of your league
cuz I mean if you're a man you know
there's not a woman on earth as gross as
you right I mean we can admit that
that's pretty
true so 35 years a long time people want
to know what the secret is to being
married I I think it's funny they ask me
I'm not sure what the secret is I uh
this is my trick if it helps I never got
divorced I know I know it seems obvious
but that's that's that's what I did my
brother got divorced and it just looked
like too much
paperwork if I'm not going to follow my
taxes I'm certainly not going to go
through that right uh makes no sense at
all so laziness I guess is one of the
secrets quality time that's what a lot
of people say quality time is important
when we got married I was in the
military I was in the Navy and I was
deployed all the time and uh now you
know I do this for a living so I'm
usually on the road well not in the last
year so I've been home a lot more and I
can tell you this quantity time is not
the secret to good marriage but quality
time is so when I when I am home I want
to make sure we go out on date night we
have quality time right so I'll take my
wife out we I'll like take her to dinner
or something and she'll go I got to tell
you my wife will go anywhere I want
she's not picky she'll go anywhere I
want to go eat her only rule is it can't
be one of the first seven places I
suggest I don't know I don't know
why and then we we go out this is so
funny my she does this all the time it's
a weird thing she has but find a lot of
women that do this
we'll go out and she'll observe other
couples and then she'll tell me what's
going on with them right yeah she oh
look they're on their first date sure at
sad things are going you don't know them
at all what are you talking about she
she'll point out older couples always
the same thing with an older couple look
at that I'll bet they're on like their
50th Anniversary it's so sweet and she
always says this so sad though they're
just sitting there staring and eating
they're not even talking and I'm just
thinking that would be awesome when does
that start
happening I'd love to know when that
starts I'm very curious you know what
does steak taste like if you're not
choking it down with I'm sorry I don't
know kind of
cool and we don't have to go out for our
quality time we can stay in we'll stay
in you know and have um you know watch
TV play a game something my wife loves
playing games that's her favorite thing
we'll do that and her favorite game
you've play if you've married you if you
get married that you've played this game
it's uh it's her favorite game it's
called guess why I'm upset you ever play
that that's a hoot isn't it I've never
beat her 35 years I've never won not one
time I uh I I'm not even sure what the
rules are to be honest with
you
so